

VLADIMIR — —— NIKITIN

CONTACTS

Ukraine, Chernihiv

Cell: +38 (093) 551 44 74

Email: worlddesign1987@gmail.com











PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- React
- Redux
- · React hooks
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- axios
- thunk
- REST API
- Git
- Jest unit tests/storybook
- HTML5
- CSS3/SCSS

LANGUAGES

English Pre-intermediate

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Hello, I am a person who is very into programming.

I have experience in creating SPA with React / Redux / TypeScript. Now I am improving my skills in this direction and expanding them with new technologies. I'm planing to learn React-native because mobile development is very important these days. and I also want to improve my English so that I can communicate freely and understand the interlocutor.

I spend my free time developing as a web developer.

WORK HISTORY

FRONT-END DEVELOPER, FREELANCE

FEBRUARY 2021 - PRESENT

- Refactoring, bug fixing
- Migration to Typescript
- Fixed bugs related to side effects (using React.memo, useCallback, useEffect cleanup)
- React development using redux, react-redux, react-router-dom, redux-thunk, axios

WOODWORKING WORKSHOP FOREMAN

OCTOBER 2020 TO JUNE 2021

- my tasks included planning the working day for all employees
- quality control/Improving product quality
- daily reporting in 1C
- introduction of piecework wages
- process automation

CNC MACHINES OPERATOR

MAY 2014 TO OCTOBER 2020

- spelling control programs
- production of parts according to drawings
- equipment setup

EDUCATION

IT-INCUBATOR | 2020 - 2021

React Developer (React/Redux/TypeScript)

ITGID | 2020

JavaScript/HTML5/CSS